zerolag.com 2015-06-09

# Privacy Policy, Managed Hosting Services - ZeroLag Hosting

### ZeroLag Communications Privacy Policy

ZeroLag Communications, Inc. takes your privacy seriously, and has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to online privacy. Keep reading to learn more about our information gathering and dissemination practices, and our use of personally identifiable information.

### Safe Harbor

ZeroLag Communications, Inc. complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. ZeroLag Communications, Inc. has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view ZeroLag Communications, Inc.’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>

### IP Addresses

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our site or web server, and for the general administration of our website.

### Cookies

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer’s hard drive by a webpage server. Cookies are used to store and to record session information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any Personal Information you submit while on our site.

### Information Gathering

This web site collects online contact information via web inquiry forms and registration forms. The information collected may be used to send the user information about our company, or to get in touch with the user when necessary. Emails may come from ZeroLag.com

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the opt-out/modify section below.

### Security

This web site has security measures in place to protect against loss, misuse and/or alteration of the information that you provide. Furthermore, we have taken every precaution technically possible to prevent any unauthorized access to the contents of this web server.

### Opt-Out/Modify

ZeroLag provides every user with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving future communications from us, change and modify information previously provided, or remove their information from our databases altogether. You may do so in any of the following ways:

1\. Email:

2\. US Mail:

ZeroLag Communications, Inc.  
289 S. Robertson Blvd #441  
Beverly Hills, CA 90211

### Contacting ZeroLag

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this web site, or your dealings with this web site, please contact us via one of the methods above.

_This Privacy Policy was last updated Oct 17, 2014_
